https://www.maa.org/privacy-policy

Shops
About MAAMAA HistoryMAA CentennialMathDLSpotlight: Archives of American MathematicsMAA OfficersGovernanceCouncil and CommitteesBoard of DirectorsGovernance DocumentsBylawsPolicies and ProceduresPolicy on Conflict of InterestStatement about Conflict of InterestRecording or Broadcasting of MAA EventsPolicy for Establishing Endowments and FundsWelcoming Environment, Code of Ethics, and Whistleblower PolicyAvoiding Implicit BiasCopyright AgreementPrincipal Investigator's ManualAdvocacySupport MAAPlanned GivingThe Icosahedron SocietyOur PartnersAdvertise with MAAEmployment OpportunitiesStaff DirectoryContact Us2019 Impact ReportMembershipMembership CategoriesBecome a MemberMembership RenewalMember Discount ProgramsNASA Federal Credit UnionMERCER InsuranceMAA Member LookupNew Member BenefitsMAA PublicationsPeriodicalsThe American Mathematical MonthlyMathematics MagazineThe College Mathematics JournalLoci/JOMABrowseHow to CiteCommunications in Visual MathematicsConvergenceAbout ConvergenceWhat's in Convergence?Convergence ArticlesImages for Classroom UseMathematical TreasuresPortrait GalleryPaul R. Halmos Photograph CollectionOther ImagesCritics CornerQuotationsProblems from Another TimeConference CalendarGuidelines for Convergence AuthorsMAA FOCUSMath HorizonsSubmissions to MAA PeriodicalsGuide for RefereesMAA Press (an imprint of the AMS)MAA NotesMAA ReviewsBrowseMAA Library RecommendationsAdditional Sources for Math Book ReviewsAbout MAA ReviewsMathematical CommunicationInformation for LibrariesAuthor ResourcesAdvertise with MAAMeetingsMAA MathFestExhibitor ProspectusCalendar of EventsFuture MeetingsMAA Distinguished Lecture SeriesJoint Mathematics MeetingsPropose a SessionProposal and Abstract DeadlinesMAA PoliciesInvited Paper Session ProposalsThemed Contributed Paper Session ProposalsPanel, Poster, Town Hall, and Workshop ProposalsMinicourse ProposalsMAA Section MeetingsCarriage House Meeting SpaceMAA Carriage House ScheduleRates and Room CapacitiesMeeting Request FormCateringMathFest ArchiveMathFest Programs ArchiveMathFest Abstract ArchiveHistorical SpeakersWelcoming Environment PolicyCompetitionsAbout AMCFAQsInformation for School AdministratorsInformation for Students and Parents2020-2021 AMC Online PoliciesHow to Register for the AMC OnlineAMC PoliciesAMC 8AMC 10/12AMC InternationalInvitational CompetitionsAdditional Competition LocationsImportant Dates for AMCRegistrationPutnam CompetitionPutnam Competition ArchiveAMC ResourcesCurriculum InspirationsSliffe AwardMAA K-12 BenefitsMailing List RequestsStatistics & AwardsPrograms and CommunitiesCurriculum ResourcesClassroom Capsules and NotesBrowseCommon VisionCourse CommunitiesBrowseINGenIOuSInstructional Practices GuideMobius MAA Test PlacementMETA MathMETA Math Webinar May 2020Progress through CalculusSurvey and ReportsMember CommunitiesMAA SectionsSection MeetingsDeadlines and FormsPrograms and ServicesEditor Lectures ProgramPólya LectureshipSection Visitors ProgramPolicies and ProceduresGuidelines for Section WebmastersSection ResourcesGuidelines for the Section Secretary and TreasurerHigh School TeachersSIGMAAJoining a SIGMAAForming a SIGMAAHistory of SIGMAASIGMAA Officer HandbookFrequently Asked QuestionsGraduate StudentsStudentsMeetings and Conferences for StudentsJMM Student Poster SessionInformation for JudgesPast Sessions and WinnersPoster InformationJMM Poster SessionUndergraduate ResearchOpportunities to PresentInformation and ResourcesUndergraduate Research ResourcesMathFest Student Paper SessionsResearch Experiences for UndergraduatesStudent Poster Session FAQsStudent ResourcesHigh SchoolUndergraduateFun MathReading ListMAA AwardsAwards BookletsWriting AwardsCarl B. Allendoerfer AwardsChauvenet PrizesRegulations Governing the Association's Award of The Chauvenet PrizeTrevor Evans AwardsPaul R. Halmos - Lester R. Ford AwardsMerten M. Hasse PrizeGeorge Pólya AwardsDavid P. Robbins PrizeBeckenbach Book PrizeEuler Book PrizeDaniel Solow Author’s AwardTeaching AwardsHenry L. Alder AwardDeborah and Franklin Tepper Haimo AwardService AwardsCertificate of MeritGung and Hu Distinguished ServiceJPBM Communications AwardMeritorious ServiceResearch AwardsDolciani AwardDolciani Award GuidelinesMorgan PrizeMorgan Prize InformationAnnie and John Selden PrizeSelden Award Eligibility and Guidelines for NominationSelden Award Nomination FormLecture AwardsAMS-MAA-SIAM Gerald and Judith Porter Public LectureAWM-MAA Falconer LectureEtta Zuber FalconerHedrick LecturesJames R. C. Leitzel LecturePólya LecturePólya Lecturer InformationPutnam Competition Individual and Team WinnersThe D. E. Shaw Group AMC 8 Awards & CertificatesMaryam Mirzakhani AMC 10A Prize and AwardsTwo Sigma AMC 10B Awards & CertificatesJane Street AMC 12A Awards & CertificatesBlogsDevlin's AngleLaunchingsCard ColmTeaching with TechTeaching TidbitsMAAMinuteMathMAANumber A DayMAA Found MathMAA Found Math Gallery 2015MAA Found Math Gallery 2014MAA Found Math Gallery 2013MAA Found Math Gallery 2012MAA Found Math Gallery 2011MAA Found Math Gallery 2010MAA Found Math Gallery 2009MAA Found Math Gallery 2008MAA Found Math Gallery 2007AftermathMathematical TreasuresMAA BooksMathematical CommunicationInnovative Teaching ExchangeMAA ConnectOutreach InitiativesDolciani Mathematics Enrichment GrantsDMEG AwardeesNational Research Experience for Undergraduates Program (NREUP)Tensor SUMMA GrantsTensor Women & Mathematics GrantsProfessional Development"Best Practices" StatementsCoMInDSData Science WorkshopsPIC MathCourse ResourcesIndustrial Math Case StudiesParticipating FacultyPIC Math 2020 Student ShowcasePIC Math Workshops on Data ScienceProject NExTFellowsApplicationDates and LocationsPast ProgramsLeadership TeamSupport Project NExTSection NExTStatPREPTondeur Career InitiativesVITAL Faculty Pilot ProgramVirtual ProgrammingNewsOur BlogMAA Social MediaRSSOn This DayCOVID-19 Update
You are hereHome » Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
May 11, 2018
This is the Mathematical Association of America (MAA) website Privacy Policy, which discloses the privacy practices of maa.org. The following principles govern our information practices and other privacy aspects of our website.
Protecting Your Information
At MAA, protecting the privacy of our members and customers is important. We encrypt the transmission of sensitive (such as credit card numbers) information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We protect your personal information from loss, misuse or unauthorized alteration by using industry-recognized security safeguards. We use both internal and external resources to review our security procedures. We follow industry-recognized standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once received. We cannot guarantee its absolute security as no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is completely secure but we are committed to safeguarding your sensitive information. If you have any questions about the security on our website, contact maaservice@maa.org.
Data Retention
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, contact maaservice@maa.org. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
How We Use Your Information
When we ask you for information on our website, we will tell you how the information you provide will be used. You retain the right to opt-out of communications that are not transactional at anytime.
Our Relationships With Third Parties
We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.
We have limited relationships with third parties to assist us in servicing you, for example, by fulfilling customer orders, providing customer service or delivering subscription content. These service providers are contractually required to maintain the confidentiality of the information we provide them. When you request any of these products or services, you permit us to provide your personal information to the contractor to fulfill your request. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.
We may disclose your information if we are required to by a law enforcement action such as a court order, subpoena, or search warrant or similar legal process. We may also disclose your information when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.
If MAA is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.
How We Use Web Technology
Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts or similar technologies are used by MAA and our partners (our marketing partners), affiliates, or analytics or service providers (providers of our online and mobile version of MAA magazines; job listing host site; etc). These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.
We use cookies for [our shopping cart, to remember users’ settings (e.g. language preference), for authentication]. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.
We gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. This automatically collected data is assigned a generic session ID and is not linked to specific users.
Our website includes social media features, such as the Facebook “like” button [and widgets, such as the “share this” button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.
Your Contact Information
We may use your contact information to tell you about other products we think might interest you. Specifically, with your consent we sell this information to third parties we feel may provide goods and services that may be of interest to our members. If you do not want us to share your personal information with these companies, contact us at maaservice@maa.org.
Our site includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of MAA. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit.
If your personal information changes or if you no longer desire our services, you can update, delete, or correct your personal information relating to your membership, member directory, email, and newsletter preferences by logging into maa.org and selecting the appropriate tab on the My Profile page or by contacting Customer Service at 1-800-331-1622 or email maaservice@maa.org.
If you have questions regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact:
MAA Press (an imprint of the AMS)
